[
  {
    "id": 2401,
    "question": "central",
    "questionDetails": "La central no genera suficiente electricidad para abastecer a toda la ciudad.",
    "answer": "power station, core, headquarters",
    "answerDetails": "The power station doesn’t generate enough electricity to power the whole city."
  },
  {
    "id": 2402,
    "question": "ocurrido",
    "questionDetails": "Y que el fallo había ocurrido por esas alteraciones.",
    "answer": "occurred, happened, transpired",
    "answerDetails": "And that the failure occurred because of those alterations."
  },
  {
    "id": 2403,
    "question": "responde",
    "questionDetails": "Veamos si el universo responde.",
    "answer": "responds, answer, replies",
    "answerDetails": "Let us see if the universe responds."
  },
  {
    "id": 2404,
    "question": "descanso",
    "questionDetails": "Un breve descanso entre ejercicios es esencial para un entrenamiento óptimo.",
    "answer": "rest, break, relaxation",
    "answerDetails": "A short rest between exercises is essential for an optimum workout."
  },
  {
    "id": 2405,
    "question": "míralo",
    "answer": "Look"
  },
  {
    "id": 2406,
    "question": "convertido",
    "questionDetails": "Dicen que ha convertido a cientos más.",
    "answer": "converted",
    "answerDetails": "They say he converted hundreds more."
  },
  {
    "id": 2407,
    "question": "estaríamos",
    "questionDetails": "Todos estaríamos como clase mucho mejor situados.",
    "answer": "would",
    "answerDetails": "The whole class would do better."
  },
  {
    "id": 2408,
    "question": "inútil",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre he sido inútil en la cocina.",
    "answer": "useless, futile, worthless",
    "answerDetails": "I’ve always been useless in the kitchen."
  },
  {
    "id": 2409,
    "question": "decidimos",
    "questionDetails": "Decidimos que nuestro único rival es el teatro.",
    "answer": "decided",
    "answerDetails": "We have decided our only rival is the theatre."
  },
  {
    "id": 2410,
    "question": "empiezan",
    "questionDetails": "Las piezas empiezan a encajar.",
    "answer": "begin, start",
    "answerDetails": "The final pieces begin to fall into shape."
  },
  {
    "id": 2411,
    "question": "subiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Y está subiendo el índice de audiencia.",
    "answer": "climbing, rising, up",
    "answerDetails": "And our ratings are climbing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2412,
    "question": "pablo",
    "answer": "Pablo"
  },
  {
    "id": 2413,
    "question": "princesa",
    "questionDetails": "La princesa de la política americana.",
    "answer": "princess",
    "answerDetails": "The princess of American politics."
  },
  {
    "id": 2414,
    "question": "barco",
    "questionDetails": "Como tenemos una casa en la costa, estamos pensando en comprarnos un barco.",
    "answer": "boat, ship, vessel",
    "answerDetails": "Since we live on the coast, we’re thinking about buying a boat."
  },
  {
    "id": 2415,
    "question": "ayudes",
    "answer": "help"
  },
  {
    "id": 2416,
    "question": "investigando",
    "questionDetails": "Estamos investigando la causa ahora.",
    "answer": "investigating, researching, inquiring",
    "answerDetails": "We are investigating the cause."
  },
  {
    "id": 2417,
    "question": "estúpido",
    "questionDetails": "¡ No eres un cobarde, estúpido!.",
    "answer": "stupid",
    "answerDetails": "You’re not a coward, stupid!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2418,
    "question": "salgan",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos ordenado a todos que salgan de la ciudad.",
    "answer": "out",
    "answerDetails": "We have ordered everyone out of the city."
  },
  {
    "id": 2419,
    "question": "buscarla",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces, ve a buscarla.",
    "answer": "her",
    "answerDetails": "Then go get her."
  },
  {
    "id": 2420,
    "question": "montar",
    "questionDetails": "Montaron cañones a ambos lados del barco de guerra.",
    "answer": "mount, ride",
    "answerDetails": "They mounted guns on both sides of the battleship."
  },
  {
    "id": 2421,
    "question": "arrepentir",
    "questionDetails": "Si te juntas con él, te vas a arrepentir.",
    "answer": "regret",
    "answerDetails": "You hook up with him and you’ll regret it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2422,
    "question": "sigas",
    "questionDetails": "Prende de ellos, pero no los sigas.",
    "answer": "follow",
    "answerDetails": "Learn from them, but do not follow."
  },
  {
    "id": 2423,
    "question": "haberme",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca debí haberme ido.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "I should have never gone away."
  },
  {
    "id": 2424,
    "question": "aguanto",
    "questionDetails": "Ya no aguanto esta ropa.",
    "answer": "stand",
    "answerDetails": "I can’t stand these clothes anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 2425,
    "question": "mentiroso",
    "answer": "lying"
  },
  {
    "id": 2426,
    "question": "organizar",
    "questionDetails": "Subí al ático para organizarlo y me ensucié.",
    "answer": "organize, arrange",
    "answerDetails": "I went up to organize the attic and I got dirty."
  },
  {
    "id": 2427,
    "question": "personaje",
    "questionDetails": "Mi abuela era todo un personaje.",
    "answer": "character",
    "answerDetails": "My grandmother was a real character."
  },
  {
    "id": 2428,
    "question": "encantada",
    "questionDetails": "Encantada de conocerle, señor.",
    "answer": "delighted, enchanted, haunted",
    "answerDetails": "Delighted to have met you, sire."
  },
  {
    "id": 2429,
    "question": "alcanza",
    "questionDetails": "Es que alcanza a pensar en el más mínimo detalle.",
    "answer": "reaches, achieves, attains",
    "answerDetails": "It reaches to think in the smallest detail."
  },
  {
    "id": 2430,
    "question": "pensaste",
    "questionDetails": "Tú pensaste que no había ido a verte bailar.",
    "answer": "thought, youthought",
    "answerDetails": "You thought she didn’t come to see you dance."
  },
  {
    "id": 2431,
    "question": "caballeros",
    "questionDetails": "Gracias por el whisky, caballeros.",
    "answer": "gentlemen, knights, gents",
    "answerDetails": "Thanks for the drink, gentlemen."
  },
  {
    "id": 2432,
    "question": "muriendo",
    "questionDetails": "El sol de este sistema está muriendo.",
    "answer": "dying, dyin’",
    "answerDetails": "The sun in this system is dying."
  },
  {
    "id": 2433,
    "question": "dirá",
    "questionDetails": "Tu amigo te dirá los detalles.",
    "answer": "tell",
    "answerDetails": "Your friend will tell you the details."
  },
  {
    "id": 2434,
    "question": "tratamiento",
    "questionDetails": "El tratamiento del tejido elimina las cualidades no deseadas.",
    "answer": "processing",
    "answerDetails": "The processing of the fabric eliminates undesirable qualities."
  },
  {
    "id": 2435,
    "question": "diera",
    "questionDetails": "Me pidió que le diera esta carta.",
    "answer": "give",
    "answerDetails": "He asked me to give you this letter."
  },
  {
    "id": 2436,
    "question": "magia",
    "questionDetails": "De repente, como por la magia, las puertas comienzan a abrirse.",
    "answer": "magic",
    "answerDetails": "Suddenly, as if by magic, the doors start to open."
  },
  {
    "id": 2437,
    "question": "tenerlo",
    "questionDetails": "Ese coche deportivo es increíble. Haría cualquier cosa por tenerlo.",
    "answer": "have it",
    "answerDetails": "That sports car is amazing. I’d do anything to have it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2438,
    "question": "paquete",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes comprar el software como paquete y ahorrar dinero en cada artículo.",
    "answer": "bundle",
    "answerDetails": "You can buy the software as a bundle and save money on each individual item."
  },
  {
    "id": 2439,
    "question": "ocasión",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos tenido ocasión de aumentar.",
    "answer": "occasion",
    "answerDetails": "We had occasion to raise it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2440,
    "question": "sacaron",
    "questionDetails": "Ellos me sacaron de mi casa.",
    "answer": "took",
    "answerDetails": "They took me from my house."
  },
  {
    "id": 2441,
    "question": "techo",
    "questionDetails": "La lluvia lo despertó, martilleando en el techo.",
    "answer": "roof",
    "answerDetails": "The rain woke him, hammering on the roof."
  },
  {
    "id": 2442,
    "question": "plato",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuántas veces te he dicho que quites tu plato de la mesa cuando termines?",
    "answer": "dish, plate, platter",
    "answerDetails": "How many times have I told you to remove your dish from the table when you’ve finished?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2443,
    "question": "profundo",
    "questionDetails": "La empresa busca contratar a alguien con conocimiento profundo de la soldadura.",
    "answer": "thorough, intense",
    "answerDetails": "The company seeks to hire someone with a thorough knowledge of welding."
  },
  {
    "id": 2444,
    "question": "abro",
    "questionDetails": "Abro con un dólar.",
    "answer": "open",
    "answerDetails": "Open for a buck."
  },
  {
    "id": 2445,
    "question": "imágenes",
    "questionDetails": "La cámara en realidad produce imágenes increíbles.",
    "answer": "imagery",
    "answerDetails": "This camera actually produces incredible imagery."
  },
  {
    "id": 2446,
    "question": "olor",
    "questionDetails": "27 gatos vivieron allí-se puede imaginar el olor!.",
    "answer": "smell, scent",
    "answerDetails": "27 cats lived there—you can imagine the smell!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2447,
    "question": "trabajado",
    "questionDetails": "Ya has trabajado bastante por hoy.",
    "answer": "worked, labored",
    "answerDetails": "I worked you enough for one day."
  },
  {
    "id": 2448,
    "question": "traía",
    "questionDetails": "Los traía aquí constantemente.",
    "answer": "brought",
    "answerDetails": "Brought them in here all the time."
  },
  {
    "id": 2449,
    "question": "acabado",
    "questionDetails": "El acabado del escritorio de tu abuelo quedó muy bien.",
    "answer": "finish",
    "answerDetails": "The finish on your grandfather’s desk came out really well."
  },
  {
    "id": 2450,
    "question": "cincuenta",
    "answer": "fifties"
  },
  {
    "id": 2451,
    "question": "original",
    "questionDetails": "El filme original tenía otro nombre.",
    "answer": "original",
    "answerDetails": "The original was a different name."
  },
  {
    "id": 2452,
    "question": "mejorar",
    "questionDetails": "Esfuerzos para mejorar las relaciones entre los países.",
    "answer": "improve",
    "answerDetails": "Efforts to improve relations between the countries."
  },
  {
    "id": 2453,
    "question": "entré",
    "questionDetails": "Simplemente entré a un concesionario y lo compré.",
    "answer": "walked",
    "answerDetails": "Just walked onto a lot and bought it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2454,
    "question": "llevé",
    "questionDetails": "Me llevé buenas palizas.",
    "answer": "took",
    "answerDetails": "I took some massive beatings there."
  },
  {
    "id": 2455,
    "question": "decías",
    "questionDetails": "En cuanto a lo que decías de tener hijos.",
    "answer": "said, kept saying",
    "answerDetails": "What you said about having children."
  },
  {
    "id": 2456,
    "question": "fila",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestros asientos están en la fila doce.",
    "answer": "row, line, rank",
    "answerDetails": "Our seats are in row 12."
  },
  {
    "id": 2457,
    "question": "intenta",
    "questionDetails": "Pobrecita Sheila. Intenta ingresar al maratón todos los años, pero nunca gana la lotería.",
    "answer": "she tries",
    "answerDetails": "Poor Sheila. She tries to get into the marathon every year, but never wins the lottery."
  },
  {
    "id": 2458,
    "question": "aquellos",
    "questionDetails": "Los mejores amigos son aquellos que están siempre ahí para tí.",
    "answer": "ones",
    "answerDetails": "The best friends are the ones who are always there for you."
  },
  {
    "id": 2459,
    "question": "distintos",
    "questionDetails": "La policía allanó una bodega para detener a los distintos miembros de una pandilla local.",
    "answer": "various",
    "answerDetails": "The police raided a warehouse in order to arrest the various members of a local gang."
  },
  {
    "id": 2460,
    "question": "video",
    "questionDetails": "El video muestra que el padre intentó detenerlo.",
    "answer": "video, tape",
    "answerDetails": "The video shows the father tried to stop it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2461,
    "question": "oíste",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que me oíste llamarte pero escogiste ignorarme.",
    "answer": "you heard, did you hear",
    "answerDetails": "I know you heard me calling you, but you chose to ignore me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2462,
    "question": "perra",
    "questionDetails": "Esa perra está tras mi marido.",
    "answer": "skank",
    "answerDetails": "That skank is after my man."
  },
  {
    "id": 2463,
    "question": "política",
    "questionDetails": "Nos oponemos a la política del gobierno de repatriar a niños inmigrantes a su país de orígen.",
    "answer": "policy",
    "answerDetails": "We oppose the government’s policy of sending migrant children back to their country of origin."
  },
  {
    "id": 2464,
    "question": "sexo",
    "questionDetails": "Usar el sexo como una escapatoria.",
    "answer": "sex, gender, laid",
    "answerDetails": "Using sex as an escape."
  },
  {
    "id": 2465,
    "question": "relájate",
    "questionDetails": "Ahora, relájate y sonríe.",
    "answer": "relax, chill out, chillax",
    "answerDetails": "Now relax and smile."
  },
  {
    "id": 2466,
    "question": "redes",
    "questionDetails": "Las redes sociales han estado siempre ahí.",
    "answer": "networks",
    "answerDetails": "Social networks have always been there."
  },
  {
    "id": 2467,
    "question": "horror",
    "questionDetails": "Me senté con horror congelado durante un minuto o dos.",
    "answer": "horror",
    "answerDetails": "I sat frozen with horror for a minute or two."
  },
  {
    "id": 2468,
    "question": "echando",
    "questionDetails": "Mira toda la culpa que te esta echando encima.",
    "answer": "throwing, casting, pouring",
    "answerDetails": "Look at the guilt he’s throwing your way."
  },
  {
    "id": 2469,
    "question": "metiste",
    "questionDetails": "Te metiste con mi lista.",
    "answer": "messed, get",
    "answerDetails": "You messed with my list item."
  },
  {
    "id": 2470,
    "question": "paseo",
    "questionDetails": "Si usted está en su y tiene que hacer el paseo temido de la vergüenza de casa, el acero usted mismo.",
    "answer": "walk, stroll, drive",
    "answerDetails": "If you’re at his and have to make the dreaded walk of shame home, steel yourself."
  },
  {
    "id": 2471,
    "question": "macho",
    "questionDetails": "Los pingüinos machos les dan guijarros a sus compañeras como regalos.",
    "answer": "male",
    "answerDetails": "Male Penguins give pebbles to their mates as gifts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2472,
    "question": "salvó",
    "questionDetails": "Ella dijo que le salvó la vida.",
    "answer": "saved, spared",
    "answerDetails": "She says you saved her life."
  },
  {
    "id": 2473,
    "question": "vivos",
    "questionDetails": "Flores eran para los vivos.",
    "answer": "living",
    "answerDetails": "Flowers were for the living."
  },
  {
    "id": 2474,
    "question": "pensó",
    "answer": "Thought"
  },
  {
    "id": 2475,
    "question": "metes",
    "questionDetails": "Te metes con el, y me respondes a mi.",
    "answer": "mess, get, tuck",
    "answerDetails": "You mess with him, you answer to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2476,
    "question": "pudieron",
    "questionDetails": "Hicieron todo lo que pudieron.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "They did everything they could do."
  },
  {
    "id": 2477,
    "question": "reloj",
    "questionDetails": "Adelantar/atrasar el reloj.",
    "answer": "clock, watch",
    "answerDetails": "To put the clock forward/back."
  },
  {
    "id": 2478,
    "question": "acceso",
    "questionDetails": "Nos negaron el acceso a nuestro nieto.",
    "answer": "access",
    "answerDetails": "We were denied access to our grandson."
  },
  {
    "id": 2479,
    "question": "registro",
    "questionDetails": "Bob trabaja en la sección inmobiliaria del registro.",
    "answer": "registry, log, register",
    "answerDetails": "Bob works in the property section of the registry."
  },
  {
    "id": 2480,
    "question": "copia",
    "questionDetails": "Puedo darte una copia de todos mis registros de pagos.",
    "answer": "copy",
    "answerDetails": "I can get you a copy of my payroll records."
  },
  {
    "id": 2481,
    "question": "trajeron",
    "questionDetails": "Invitamos a los vecinos a cenar. Ellos trajeron las bebidas y nosotros cocinamos.",
    "answer": "they brought",
    "answerDetails": "We invited the neighbors over for dinner. They brought the drinks and we cooked."
  },
  {
    "id": 2482,
    "question": "bailando",
    "questionDetails": "Ha comenzado la música y ahora estarán bailando.",
    "answer": "dancing, dancin’",
    "answerDetails": "The music has started and now they’ll be dancing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2483,
    "question": "impresión",
    "questionDetails": "Tener la impresión de que ….",
    "answer": "impression",
    "answerDetails": "To be under the impression that…."
  },
  {
    "id": 2484,
    "question": "buscas",
    "questionDetails": "Y de esa forma, ganarás el apoyo que buscas.",
    "answer": "seek, want",
    "answerDetails": "And by such, gain the favor you seek."
  },
  {
    "id": 2485,
    "question": "estarás",
    "questionDetails": "Supongo que no estarás bailando con las estrellas.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "Guess you won’t be dancing with the stars."
  },
  {
    "id": 2486,
    "question": "favorito",
    "questionDetails": "Los favoritos te ayudan a guardar sitios web a los que quieres regresar más tarde.",
    "answer": "bookmark",
    "answerDetails": "Bookmarks allow you to save Web sites that you want to come back to later."
  },
  {
    "id": 2487,
    "question": "entrado",
    "questionDetails": "No digas que hemos entrado.",
    "answer": "entered, stepped",
    "answerDetails": "Do not say that we have entered."
  },
  {
    "id": 2488,
    "question": "cerrada",
    "questionDetails": "Mentira, la puerta estaba cerrada.",
    "answer": "closed, shut, locked",
    "answerDetails": "The door was closed."
  },
  {
    "id": 2489,
    "question": "pendejo",
    "questionDetails": "Deberías ser un pendejo.",
    "answer": "prick",
    "answerDetails": "You should be a prick."
  },
  {
    "id": 2490,
    "question": "siéntese",
    "questionDetails": "Acerque esa silla y siéntese aquí a mi lado.",
    "answer": "sit down, sit",
    "answerDetails": "Pull up that chair and sit down next to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2491,
    "question": "drogas",
    "questionDetails": "No compres las drogas.",
    "answer": "drugs, dope",
    "answerDetails": "Do not buy the drugs."
  },
  {
    "id": 2492,
    "question": "armar",
    "questionDetails": "Se armaron con espadas y escudos para la batalla.",
    "answer": "arm",
    "answerDetails": "They armed themselves with swords and shields for the battle."
  },
  {
    "id": 2493,
    "question": "show",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos un trato para un show.",
    "answer": "act",
    "answerDetails": "We got a deal for one act."
  },
  {
    "id": 2494,
    "question": "abogados",
    "questionDetails": "Y usted sabe el problema con los abogados.",
    "answer": "lawyers, attorneys, solicitors",
    "answerDetails": "And you know the problem with the lawyers."
  },
  {
    "id": 2495,
    "question": "pendientes",
    "questionDetails": "Los pendientes con corazones de diamante.",
    "answer": "earrings, pending, slopes",
    "answerDetails": "The earrings with the diamond hearts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2496,
    "question": "maté",
    "questionDetails": "Ya te maté una vez.",
    "answer": "killed",
    "answerDetails": "I killed you once."
  },
  {
    "id": 2497,
    "question": "maleta",
    "questionDetails": "Por causa de la maleta.",
    "answer": "suitcase",
    "answerDetails": "Because of the suitcase."
  },
  {
    "id": 2498,
    "question": "cobrar",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuánto me vas a cobrar por la comida?",
    "answer": "charge, collect, levy",
    "answerDetails": "How much are you going to charge for the meal?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2499,
    "question": "caballo",
    "questionDetails": "Puedo estar allá con mi caballo.",
    "answer": "horse",
    "answerDetails": "He could have been out there with my horse."
  },
  {
    "id": 2500,
    "question": "dispuesta",
    "questionDetails": "Ella estaba dispuesta a tomar de esa manera.",
    "answer": "willing, arranged, ready",
    "answerDetails": "She was willing to take it that way."
  }
]